I won't delete it
Prepare the Gu family's statement
Cheng Ze let's talk this out
You lost control last night
That's all the public will see
So you're blaming me
I gave you a chance
If you really post it
The Su family will be implicated too
The Su family being implicated
Isn't because I revealed the truth
It's because last night you
Agreed to call off the engagement
Su Mingyao don't you dare
Stop trying to pressure me with your words
Ah
Knowing the wedding ring details
Shows how calm she was
No crying or making a fuss
Just dropping the evidence
That's real class
Hmm
Ah
Mr Liu this is a personal misunderstanding
Please let me explain
Why did you have to
Push me into the storm too
Did I force you to wear the ring in the video